berkeleycollege.edu 2017-06-07

# Last Modified on April 14, 2017

                                                               Last Modified on April 14, 2017
                                                Berkeley College
                                                  Privacy Policy
Purpose
Berkeley College understands that your privacy is important. We want you to know what information we
may collect through our website, mobile website, mobile applications, and Short Message Service
(“SMS”) (collectively, the “Services”) and how it may be used. Continued use of the Services
constitutes your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not
use the Services.
Scope
This Privacy Policy applies to anyone using the Services. Berkeley College does not knowingly collect
data from individuals under 13 years of age through its Services. If you are under the age of 13, you are
not authorized to use the Services and should immediately stop doing so.
I. Information Collected
        Visitor Information. When you visit the Berkeley College website or otherwise use the Services,
         Berkeley College’s web server and/or our third party agents automatically receives and records
         Visitor Information about you. Visitor Information may include, but is not limited to your computer
         operating system, web browser, IP address, internet service provider, mobile carrier, geo-location
         data, cookie information, the pages you visit on the site, amount of time spent on each webpage,
         and the date and time you visit the site. We do not attempt to match or link such information to an
         individual’s personal information.
              o    Google Analytics. Berkeley College uses Google Analytics, a third party service
                   provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”) to collect and track Visitor Information. Continued
                   use of the Services constitutes your consent to Google’s collection and use of your Visitor
                   Information. For details, see Google’s Terms of Service and Privacy Practices. For details
                   on how to opt-out, see Google’s Safeguarding Your Data page.
              o    Cookies. Berkeley College uses “cookies” to track browsing patterns and collect Visitor
                   Information. You may prevent or disable the use of cookies in your web browser settings.
                   However, disabling or deleting cookies may limit your ability to use the full functionality of
                   Berkeley College sites.
              o    Geo-location Data. Berkeley College and/or its third party agents may collect information
                   about your geographic location and use that to send you location-based advertising and
                   information. Most mobile devices allow you to adjust the settings to disable or prevent
                   location information from being shared.
              o    Online Tracking. Your internet browser may allow you to select a “Do Not Track” setting,
                   which sends a signal to websites that you do not want information about your internet
                   activity to be collected or tracked. Berkeley College does not respond to internet browser
                   “Do Not Track” signals.
        Personal Information. In addition to the information that is recorded automatically, we also
         collect information that you provide to us when you complete an online form or send us e-mail.
         Such information may include your full name, address, phone number, email address or other
         personally identifiable information. Berkeley College makes no representations concerning the
         reliability of information collected by, displayed on, or transmitted from this website. Berkeley
Page 1 of 3

                                                                 Last Modified on April 14, 2017
         College takes reasonable measures to protect the security of Personal Information collected in
         accordance with prevailing industry standards. Furthermore, while we take reasonable
         precautions to secure the information we gather through the site, any sharing of Personal
         Information over the internet involves some security risk. Berkeley College does not warrant that
         the information transmitted through or displayed on the site will not be accessed by unauthorized
         individuals, or that it will be delivered free of viruses or other potentially harmful material. To the
         fullest extent permitted by law, Berkeley College specifically disclaims any warranties in
         connection with the use of this website including, but not limited to, warranties of
         merchantability, non-infringement or fitness for a particular purpose.
        Short Message Service (SMS). When you enroll in Berkeley College’s Short Message Service
         (SMS), we will collect data such as your mobile phone number, mobile carrier, date, time and
         content of messages, and other information provided by you. Berkeley College may ask you to
         provide additional information, including but not limited to the dates and times you are available to
         attend events or schedule an appointment with an admissions associate, academic advisor, or
         financial aid advisor. We may use this information to further develop and improve the service.
         Your mobile carrier may also collect data from you, as reflected in its own policies. See the SMS
         Terms and Conditions: http://berkeleycollege.edu/files_bc/Berkeley_College_SMS_Terms.pdf.
II. Correcting Information
To request a change or correction to any information you have submitted to us, please contact us at
marketing@BerkeleyCollege.edu or call 800-446-5400.
III. How We May Use or Disclose Visitor Information or Personal Information
        Re-Marketing. The Visitor Information we automatically receive and record (such as your web
         browser, IP address and cookie information) may be used to facilitate “re-marketing,” a practice
         through which your visits to linked sites or advertisements may be shared with and used by our
         affiliated companies or third party advertisers to send you additional communications in which you
         may be interested. In addition, we may share Visitor Information or Personal Information about
         you with employees of Berkeley College and affiliated entities involved in activities to which it is
         relevant; with our attorneys, accountants and other professionals; and with third parties who work
         with us in developing and maintaining the Services. We may also use that Visitor Information
         and/or Personal Information for internal testing or training purposes, to help us develop our
         website to better meet visitors' needs and expectations, or to communicate with you for any
         purpose. Some Visitor Information and/or Personal Information may be stored subject to lengthy
         retention requirements.
        Disclosure to Law Enforcement. Berkeley reserves the right to disclose Visitor Information
         and/or Personal Information to law enforcement officials, investigators, or other third parties as
         we deem necessary to prevent or address abuses of the site including, but not limited to,
         violations of this Internet Privacy Policy, or when such disclosure is required by law.
        Programs of Interest. Occasionally, Berkeley College or our third party agents may use certain
         information that you have provided or we have collected to send you advertisements or
         information about programs, products or services offered by Berkeley College or other
         organizations that we think may be of interest to you. However, Berkeley College does not sell
         or rent any personal data submitted by visitors to any unrelated third parties.
Page 2 of 3

                                                               Last Modified on April 14, 2017
IV. Removals and Opt-Outs
         Remove from Mailing List. Berkeley College respects the privacy of users visiting our site and
          will abide by all applicable laws concerning the release of Personal Information. If you tell us that
          you do not wish to have this information used as a basis for further contact with you, we will
          respect your wishes. Please e-mail marketing@BerkeleyCollege.edu to request that your name
          be removed from our mailing lists.
         Opt-Out from SMS. To stop receiving text messages from the Berkeley College SMS, text STOP
          OR QUIT to 464646. See the SMS Terms and Conditions available online at
          http://berkeleycollege.edu/files_bc/Berkeley_College_SMS_Terms.pdf.
V. Links to Other Sites
This site may contain links to other sites operated by non-affiliated third parties. If you choose to access
such third-party sites, the operators of such sites may acquire access to your personal information. You
should be aware that Berkeley College does not control the information privacy and security policies or
practices of such unaffiliated third parties. Therefore, we cannot be held responsible for either the
content of such third-party sites or their use (or abuse) of any information they receive from or about you.
VI. Changes to This Policy
Berkeley College may modify this Privacy Policy at any time, without prior notice. If we choose to do so,
then the effective date of the change will be identified above the title of this document as the “Last
Modified” date. You will be deemed to have agreed to any such modifications by your continued use of
this site on or after the “Last Modified” date. We encourage you to review this policy as often as
necessary to remain aware of its current contents.
VII. Questions
Any questions concerning this Privacy Policy may be addressed to marketing@BerkeleyCollege.edu.
Page 3 of 3
